<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Life in Harmony]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Life in Harmony]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 05:01:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Life in Harmony]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Life in Harmony</h1><p>We offer clinical therapeutic services for the San Francisco community, specializing in individual, couples and group counseling.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ffa5705d038cb2f7434366e467bc4eed505323a7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/life-in-harmony/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4d732c0a-3be7-4c04-9fb0-f93ba7943479</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 04:51:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Office]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Our Office</h1><p>We are located in lovely San Francisco, California, We are blessed to enjoy such a wonderful location.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/we-are-located-in-lovely-san-francisco-california-we-are-b/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ae2e435c-ef7a-472f-8c7c-1f846c013b02</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 05:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Work Stress]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Work Stress</h1><p>An interesting articledated January 25th2006 says“A new study by researchers from UCL Epidemiology and Public Health has found that stress at work is an important factor in causing heart disease and diabetes (…) The study at University College London which was led by Dr Tarani Chandola, concludes:</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/60f1728f-179c-420e-93b4-4ea36239faf9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/c7b806b7-006b-4199-9f45-2f8813702e5d/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c7b806b7-006b-4199-9f45-2f8813702e5d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 05:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Message from Takako]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Message from Takako</h1><p>My philosophy for therapy is that we all need to find “harmony/balance” in our lives to feel happy. As a cellist in a community orchestra, I came to realize there is similarity between music and life.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/45789c7c-98f1-43d2-9715-55cc64c52f78.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/b545ee7e-7199-40c9-a531-93358f9e6812/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b545ee7e-7199-40c9-a531-93358f9e6812</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 04:51:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Family Counseling]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Family Counseling</h1><p>Have you experienced feelings of thoughts like“Why did I choose him as my partner?” “I wish I had different mother. She doesn’t understand me!” “I don’t know what to do with my son…he is a great kid at home but he always gets in trouble at school.”Sometime we feel more overwhelmed and feel helpless because we have less control over other people and its their situations.Each family has different values and expectations which shape us when we are growing up. Those inherent differences confront us when we form a new family. Sometimes, it becomes more challenging because of different cultural principles and or spiritual values. Family therapy can provide an open and safe environment to work together through acknowledging differences and learning to accepting one another.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f264f8c4-a5b4-4c12-857a-0e8f1c80a3cd.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/87d6db0d-2b19-4434-a39d-438f2c69008e/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">87d6db0d-2b19-4434-a39d-438f2c69008e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 03:54:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Couples Counseling]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Couples Counseling</h1><p>Have you felt“She was so sweet and we did everything together when we met…but she doesn’t want to do anything with me. What’s wrong with us?” “My partner is always gone and I am left alone to do all the housework!”Our relationship is constantly shaping forms and also requires constant effort to maintain “balance” and “harmony.” Life event comes with a lesson – it is so true for relationships. Some people stay in your life a short time and some stay for a long time to teach you lessons. Couples therapy provides you and your partner a safe to place to explore feelings and regain trust in relationships.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/48ab737a-d896-4b54-92d1-9bf55ab6395e.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/84b9477c-9d18-4d2a-ad5c-6a112a35f154/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">84b9477c-9d18-4d2a-ad5c-6a112a35f154</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 03:54:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Individual Counseling and Coaching]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Individual Counseling and Coaching</h1><p>Life is filled with experiences…with highs and lows, ebbs and flows, like ocean waves. Sometimes we feel“Why me?” “How did it happen to me?”We feel sadness, anger, disappointment, loneliness…sometimes we feel like “no one understands me what I am going through….” Life events such as divorce, separation, illness, layoff, bankruptcy come to us without warning. Or, getting into a new relationship, a new job or having children could add stress in your life even though they are positive factors. It is natural to struggle with adjustment and coping with stress factors in your life. Individual counseling assists you to reevaluate your strength and regain hope in your life.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/takako-ainsworth-lcsw/531bba5e-3ff2-42a7-becd-56f4b430668c/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">531bba5e-3ff2-42a7-becd-56f4b430668c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 03:52:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>